Guide to the Lesbian and Gay Liberation Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, 1969-2005; 1969-1981; Accession 2006-M-065
  - Lesbianism: A Socialist Feminist Perspective [Susan Williams; 2 versions], 1973, undated (Box 4)
  - Letters to Women, undated (Box 4)
  - Me and Them Sirens Running All Night Long [Susan Cavin], 1973 (Box 4)
  - Moods of Eros...and Other Poems... [Elsa Gidlow], undated (Box 5)
  - Moonstorm, nos. 2, 9-10, 1973 fall, 1977 spring, 1977 fall (Box 5)
  - Motive, vol. 29, no. 6/7; vol. 32, no. 1 ["On the Liberation of Women" and "Lesbian/Feminist Issue"], 1969 Mar/Apr, 1972 (Box 5)
  - No More Fun & Games, issues 1-6, 1969-1973 (Box 5)
  - No More Packaged Deals... An Anthology of Eugene Women Poets, 1976 June (Box 5)
  - Notes from the Second Year, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Notes from the Third Year, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Open and Positive: An Account of How John Warburton Came Out at School and the Consequences, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Out, vol. 1, no. 2, 1974 April (Box 5)
  - Paid My Dues, vol. 1, no. 4; vol. 2, no. 2, 1975 Mar, 1978 winter (Box 5)
  - Paragraph, no. 2, 1979 (Box 5)
  - Pearl Diver [3 issues], 1977 May, July (Box 5)
  - Pit Stop, 1975 (Box 6)
  - "Plays by Women" [compiled by Eleanor Batchelder; produced by Womanbooks], 1977 November (Box 6)
  - Pointblank Times, vol. 4, no. 1, 1978 Jan/February (Box 6)
  - Porticullis, vol. 1, nos. 1-2, 1972 January-February (Box 6)
  - Purple Star, vol. 1, no. 1, 1971 spring (Box 6)
  - Remembering Mother Stein [Carla Duke], 1971 December (Box 6)
  - The Second Wave, vol. 2, nos. 3-4; vol. 4, no. 2; vol. 6, no. 1, 1973-1981 (Box 6)
  - "She's a Jim-Dandy" [Susan Baker], undated (Box 6)
  - Sisters, vol. 4, no. 8, 1973 August (Box 6)
  - Sleeping Beauty, 1971 (Box 6)
  - A Songbook and Scrapbook of the Album [Meg Christian, I Know You Know ], 1975 (Box 6)
  - So's Your Old Lady, 6 issues including nos. 3, 6, 10, 12, 18, 1973-1977 (Box 6)
  - Soy [Zelima], 1974 (Box 6)
  - The Tide
    General note
    See: Accession 2006-M-065, 1969-2005 (inclusive), 1969-1981 (bulk) Box 3
  - These Days [Lee Lally], 1972 (Box 6)
  - 13th Moon, vol. 1, no. 2; vol. 2, no. 1, 1973-1974 (Box 6)
  - This Woman [Barbara O'Mary], 1971 October (Box 6)
  - Thunder from the Earth, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Très Femmes, vol. 1, nos. 1-2, 1972 Oct, undated (Box 6)
  - Tribe [Martha Courtot], 1977 (Box 6)
  - The Universities and the Gay Experience, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Up from Under, vol. 1, nos. 1, 4-5, 1970-1973 (Box 6)
  - Uptown's Daughters, 1977 April (Box 6)
  - "Where Will You Be?" The Professional Oppression of Gay People: A Lesbian/Feminist Perspective [Bernice Goodman], 1980 (Box 6)
  - Wild Women Don't Get the Blues [Barbara Emrys], 1977 (Box 7)
  - Womanspirit, vol. 1, no. 1-vol. 4, no. 16; vol. 5, nos. 19-20; vol. 6, nos. 22-23; vol. 7, nos. 26-28, 1974-1981 (Box 7)
  - Women and Honor: Some Notes on Lying [Adrienne Rich], 1977 (Box 7)
  - Women Poems, Love Poems [Susan Sherman], 1975 (Box 7)
  - Womyn/Friends: A Book of Poems, 1979 (Box 7)
- Additional material, 1950-1997; Accession 2007-M-071
  - Closet Ball [program], 1987 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Coronation Ball, Imperial Court de San Francisco, [program], 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Does Support for Gay Rights Spell Political Suicide?" [sponsored by the Gay Rights National Lobby and the National Gay Task Force], 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Every Tenth Person is a Homosexual" [newspaper flyer], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Flashpoint, Issue II, 1996 March (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Freedom Day Parade [program], 1991 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "If Your Constituents Ask..." [flyer], 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lesbian and Gay Anti-War Contingent [flyer], 1983 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Michelle International" [souvenir program], 1962 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - New York City, Coordinating Committee meeting [flyer], 1981 December 20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Off-Coloring Book, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Out in Old Wyoming" [postcard], 1954 December 24 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Picket Lines," by Jim Kepner [collection of poetry], 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Pride Parade and Celebration, San Francisco [program], 1997 June 28-29 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Revolutionary Socialist League, "Fight for Full Rights for Gay Youth" and untitled flyer, circa 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Save G.C.N.!" [Gay Community News flyer], 1982 July 7 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Spring Roundup," [benefit program for Long Beach M.C.C.], 1972 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sutter's Mill: Saloon and Restaurant [announcment of a preview party and gala opening], 1950 December 10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Sylvester at the Opera House" [program], 1979 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Third National Lesbian and Gay Health Conference [program], 1980 June 19-22 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "A Tribute to Morris Kight" [program of testimonial dinner of the Stonewall Democratic Club], 1979 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Twenty Five Year of Noble Deeds: A Silver Jubilee History of the Imperial Court de San Diego", 1996 July (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Welcome The Delegates And Friends of M.C.C., 5th National Conference" [program], 1974 August 5-11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Where the Action Is!" [published by Bay Area Reporter], undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Wonderland," Alameda County Imperial Empire Coronation 81 [program], 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "You're Fired!" [flyer of the Gay Rights National Lobby], 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Additional material, 1983, 1990; Accession 2010-M-021
  - "Dan White to be released from Soledad Prison", 1984 January (Box 1)
  - Dallas/Forth Worth Lambda Pages and advertisement, 2006 (Box 1)
  - A Gay Person's Guide to New England, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Gayellow pages #26, 1990 (Box 1)
  - GLAD Tidings Vol.2 No. 3, 1983 March 18 (Box 1)
  - Mattachine Society Today, 1955, 1963 (Box 1)
- Additional material, 1948-2010; Accession 2012-M-030
  - General, 1948-2010
    - "A Family of Friends: Portrait of a Lesbian Friendship Group 1921-1973, a lecture with slides by Frances Doughty" [flyer], Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ache: A Journal for Black Lesbians, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Consists of Vol. 2, No. 3 through Vol. 2, No. 5; and Vol. 3, Nos. 1 and 2.
    - ACT UP San Francisco Act Now Handbook, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - "Arcadia Bulletin", 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bisexuality in Patterns of Human Behavior: A Study of Individuals Who Indulge in Both Heterosexual and Homosexual Practices, With Comparative Data on Hermaphrodites, the Human Intersex, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - California Supreme Court: California Federation of Teachers, Lesbian Schoolworkers et al. v. March Fong Eu, Secretary of State, John V. Briggs, Real Party in Interest, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - "Castro Sweep Police Riot, October 6, 1989", 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Chinese Family Voice: A Newsletter of Chinese Family Alliance, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - "Committee to Preserve Our Sexual and Civil Liberties: Defend the Right to be Sexual, Be Safe in Your Sexuality" [pamphlet], Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Circumcision newsletters and foreskin writings, 1989, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - "Defend Gay's 'The Word'" [pamphlet], 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dyke [magazine], 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      This is the winter issue, Vol. 1, No. 1.
    - "Eroticizing Safer Sex Workship for Gay and Bisexual Men" [flyer], Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Fag Rag, Issue Number Forty-One, Circa 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - "Free to Be Gay: A Brief Look at the Bible and Homosexuality", 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - "Gay Pride / San Francisco Sunday, June 26th, 1977" [postcard] (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Gay Revolution Party Manifesto", Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Gay Rights!, Gay Games Special Edition of Wordt Vervolgd, distributed by Dutch Amnesty International, 1998 July-August (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Gays and the Federal Government, Bicentennial Conference Program, October 10-13, 1975, Washington, D.C." (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Gays in Library Land: The Gay and Lesbian Task Force of the American Library Association, The First Sixteen Years", 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Gente Comun: Material educativo para trabajo grupal Sociodrama", 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Good Vibes Gazette" [pamphlet], Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "A Guide to City Hall: City and County of San Francisco, A Resource Book for the Lesbian and Gay Community", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Hatawa [creative fiction], 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
      This is Vol. 1 and Vol. 4 only.
    - "Hetrick Martin Institute Report Card", 1991 winter (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - "Hite Research Questionnaire for Women", 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Homosexuals and Employment: "Essays on Homosexuality, Essay No. 4", 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - "In Loving Memory: Mayor George R. Moscone and Supervisor Harvey Milk, San Francisco, California", 1978 November 29 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "Lesbian Pulps: Part of Our Lost History", Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "Lesbian Love Poems: An aid to the inarticulate" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "Lesbians Organize: Wages Due Lesbians - Wages for Housework Campaign", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "Lesbian Sexual Imagery in the Fine Arts: A slide presentation by Tee Corinne" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Maine Lesbian Feminist Newsletter, 1984 March-April (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Marriage congratulations [pamphlet], Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "National Gay and Lesbian Task Force: Gay and Lesbian Town Meetings on Sex and Politics", 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "National Lesbian Workforce Exchange Project", Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "Play Fair!" [STD prevention booklet], Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "Put Protection on Your Erection" [animation flipbook], 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - "Sexuality and Identity 4: A women's conference sponsored by Identity House", 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Shamakami: Forum for South Asian Lesbians, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      This is Vol. 1, second edition.
    - Shamakami: Forum for South Asian Feminist Lesbians - "Politics of Location", 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      This is Vol. 2, No. 1.
    - Socialist Workers Party Discussion Bulletin, 1972 July (Box 2, Folder 2)
      This is Vol. 30, No. 2.
    - "Styles of Being a Lesbian in Paris 1890-1945" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The Littlest Fox [poetry anthology], Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The Root, 1971 June 28-July 12 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      This is Vol. 1, No. 12.
    - "Towards a Healthier Gay Lifestyle: What You Need to Know to Ensure Your Good Health", 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - True Colors, Inc. Sexual Minority Youth and Family Services Annual Report, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - True Colors, Inc. Sexual Minority Youth and Family Services Resource Guide, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - "Vote No on Propositions 63 and 64, Fight Bigotry" [pamphlet], Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - "Want You to Want You: A Guide for Girls", Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - "Your Thoughts and Feelings for Del and Phyllis" [get well card], Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Plays and theater companies, 1959-2008
    - "A Chorus Line", Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - "A Patriot for Me," Playbill, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      This is Vol. 6, Issue 10.
    - "A Rock Opera: The Events that Rocked the City in 1977 - 78 A.D. Is Now", Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - A Star Spangled Night for Rights, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - "A Woman of No Importance," Theatreprint, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      This is Volume XCII, Number 10.
    - An Evening with Quentin Crisp, On Stage Players Theater, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - "Angels in America", 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Angels in America: Perestroika, American Conservatory Theater, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Angels in America: Millennium Approaches, American Conservatory Theater, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - AIDS: Artists Involved with Death and Survival [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - As You Like It, The Cutting Ball Theater, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - At the Foot of the Mountain, Spring Tour, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Bad Drama by Richard Gray, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Bad Seed, Acme Famous Players, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Beach Blanket Babylon Goes to the Stars!", 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Beach Blanket Babylon", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Bent by Martin Sherman, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Bent," Playbill, 1979 November (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Bloolips in Bloo Revue" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Bloolips, Theater for the New City [pamphlet], Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Bloo Review: A Bloolips RetroSpectacle", 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Blue is for Boys, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "BOBO: The Gay Community Center, Press Release", 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Bookstore and the Blonde in 20-B" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Box 27, A Play by Michael Norman Mann", Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Boy Meets Boy: The Musical Comedy" [pamphlet], Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Boy Meets Boy, On Stage Actors Playhouse, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Brownian Movement: A Journal of 15 Nights in the Land of Enchantment", 1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "CAL Performances," Stagebill, 1999 December (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Carnival, Golden Gate Academy of Performing Arts, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "Chantons dans le Placard, Programme Officiel", 2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "Children of the Night: Timeless Secrets of a Rebellious Breed Exposed", 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Cinderella II: Happily Ever After, Theatre Artuad, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "Circle of the Serpent", 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "City Theatre of San Francisco," Art and Leisure Publication, 1979 March (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "Civil Sex: Dissent in America Has Never Gone Smoothly" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "Crimes Against Nature: A Play by Faggots about Survival", Circa 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Cycle Sluts: The 'New' All American Boys, Broadway Theatre, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "Dame Edna," California Playbill, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "Dark Scars: A Bondage Performance Piece by Mark I Chester" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Did You Come or Fake It?, Mothertongue Readers' Theatre, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "Disputed Territory: Sexploration", 1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "Dinosaurs," Bay Area Reporter, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Don't Bother Me I Can't Cope, Jon-Al Productions, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Dos Lesbos: A Play by, for, and about Perverts, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - "Equus," Playbill, 1974 October (Box 2, Folder 7)
      This is Volume 11.
    - "Family Jewels: The Making of Veronica Klaus", Circa 2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Fierce Love: Stories From Black Gay Life", Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Foodsexual: Come Out of Your Refrigerator" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Geese by Gus Weill", Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Golden Awards, San Francisco Academy of Performing Arts, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Gross Indecency: The Three Trials of Oscar Wilde," Performing Arts, 1998 January (Box 2, Folder 7)
      This is Volume 11, Number 1.
    - "Gross Indecency: The Three Trials of Oscar Wilde," Performing Arts, 1998 March (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Consists of Volume 11, Number 3.
    - Hello Dolly, Robert Michael Productions, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "High Drama," Theatre Rhinoceros 8th Season, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Holy Cow, The Angels of Light, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Homme Fatale: The Joey Stefano Story - The Fast Life and Slow Death of Gay Porn's Brightest Star", Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - " I Think I Like Girls by Leigh Fondakowski" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - It's a Man's World, Mabou Mines, Circa 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Jerker by Robert Chesley" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - " Jo: A Lesbian History Play by Sue-Ellen Case" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Journeyworker Jones by George Crowe, Tale Spinners Theater, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Journeyworker Jones: Chronicle of a Woman Electrical Apprentice Based on the Oral Histories of Tradeswomen" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Kiki and Herb Alive From Broadway, The American Conservatory Theater Performance Program, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      This is Volume 14, No. 1.
    - "Kimo's '87 Tour, Michale Greer" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - La Cage aux Folles 10th Anniversary, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "La Cage aux Folles," Playbill, Forrest Theatre, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "Go to Jail! Go Directly to Late Night Live with David Mills and Bridget Schwartz" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - " Lil' Abner, A Benefit Showing of the 1958 Musical Comedy" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Lord Alfred's Lover by Eric Bentley, Stonewall Repertory Theater, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Loving Women: A Script Celebrating Lesbian Life, Love, and Experiences, Mothertongue Reader's Theater, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "M. Butterfly," Playbill, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Yhis is Volume 88, No. 4.
    - Machinal, American Conservatory Theater Thirteenth Anniversary Season, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Mame, City Players, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "Mangrove in Performance", 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - My Blue Heaven, Theatre Rhinoceros Program, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Mythos Selections, Goodman Building Theater, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "Naked Boys Singing," Playbill, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      This is Volume 00, Number 3.
    - " Nocturnes: A Performance Piece by Christopher Beck and Roberty Chesley" [flyer], 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - "Orpheus, Les Iron" [flyer], Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Party San Francisco by David Dillon [program], 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "Party," Playbill, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      This is Volume 95, Number 4.
    - Pizza by Michele Linfante, Lilith Women's Theatre [flyer], Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Playbill, Plymouth Theatre, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Consists of Vol. 86, No. 6.
    - Pounds and Pounds of Dirt, Riot Act Theatre Company [program], Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "Prelude to a Kiss," Playbill, The Helen Hays Theatre, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      This is Vol. 90, No. 9.
    - Pride Season IV, The New Conservatory Theatre Center, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Pulp and Circumstance by Adele Prandini and Sue Zemel [program], Circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Queen of Angels by James Carroll Pickett [program], Circa 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "R Rated Women's Theatre Group Forming" [flyer], Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Richmond Jim, Theatre Rhinoceros [flyer], Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - "Simply Studded, Chocolate Baby Designs Benefit Show" [flyer], 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - The Sins of the Father by Robert Graham, Theatre Rhinoceros [flyer], Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Soul Survivor by Anthony Bruno, Theatre Rhinoceros [program], 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Speaking of Aging, Mothertongue Feminist Theater Collective [flyer], 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Speaking of Aging: A new script dedicated in memory of Baba Copper, Mothertongue Feminist Theater Collective [flyer], Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "Staircase," Playbill, Biltmore Theatre, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      This is Volume 5, Number 2.
    - Staves by Arthur Scott, Theatre Rhinoceros [flyer], Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Strangers in Paradox by Kate Bornstein, Theatre Rhinoceros [postponement notice], 2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "Sweet Bird of Youth," Playbill, Martin Beck Theatre, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      This is Vol. 3, No. 33.
    - Sweet Bird of Youth, American Bicentennial Theater, Circa 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - The "AIDS" Show: Aritsts Involved with Death and Survival, Theatre Rhinoceros [program], 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The Antiphon by Djuna Barnes, Studio Eremos [program], 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The Boy Friend by Sandy Wilson [program], 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The Boys in Cellblock Q by John C. Wall, Manstage Project [program], Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "The Boys in the Band," Playbill, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      This is Volume 4, No. 5.
    - "The Boys in the Band," by Mart Crowley, The Pittsburgh Playbill, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "The Drowsy Chaperone," Orpheum Theatre, Playbill, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      This is Volume 124, Number 7.
    - "The Gay Community Center Theatre Arts School and Repertory Theatre Company, San Francisco" [pamphlet], 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - "The Killing of Sister George," Playbill, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      This is Volume 3, Number 10.
    - "The Milk Train Doesn't Stop Here Anymore," Morosco Theatre, Playbill, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      This is Volume 1, Number 7.
    - The M.O. of M.I.: The Modus Operandi of Male Intimacy by Aaron Brown [program], 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Mystery of Irma Vep: a penny dreadful, Showbill [program], 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "The Odd Couple," Playbill, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      This is Volume 3, Number 2.
    - " The Quintissential Image, by Jane Chambers, and After Eleven, by Victor Bumbalo, Theatre Rhinoceros" [flyer], Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "The Ritz," Longacre Theatre, Playbill, 1975 March (Box 3, Folder 4)
      This is Volume 12.
    - The Ritz by Terrence McNally, Genesis Repertory Company of New Jersey [program], Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "The Shadow Box," Morosco Theatre, Playbill, 1977 May (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Sum of Us by David Stevens, Samuel French, Inc. [script], 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "The Vagina Monologues Encore Communications" [press release], 2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The West Street Gang by Doric Wilson, Theatre Rhinoceros [program], Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Woman in Black by Stephen Mallatratt, Off-Broadstreet Theatre [program], 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "Theatre Passe Muraille Winter Season", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Theatre Rhinoceros, The "AIDS" Show [pamphlet], 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Theatre Rhinoceros Sixteenth Anniversary 1993-1994 Season (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "Theatre Rhinoceros Presents 3 Plays by C.D. Arnold" [flyer], Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Theatre Rhinoceros Season 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Theatre Rhinoceros [magazine], circa 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Theatre Rhinoceros 1998-99 Season, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Theatre Rhinoceros 15th Anniversary [magazine], 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Theatre Rhinoceros: 20 Years [magazine], 1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "Theatre Rhinoceros Summer Nights" [flyer], Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Theatre Rhinoceros 1981-1982 Season (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "Theatre Rhinoceros" [subscription pamplet], 1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - " Torch Song Trilogy by Harvey Fierstein" [flyer], Circa 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "Torch Song Trilogy" by Harvey Fierstein, Performing Arts: California's Theatre and Music Magazine, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Tropical Fever in Key West by Robert Heide, Theatre for the New City [program], Circa 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Two Fools: A Cross-cultural Romance, by Terry Baum, Lilith Theater [flyer], 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Unfinished Business: The New A.I.D.S. Show, Theatre Rhinoceros [program], Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "Uprising...Rising Up!: A Trio of Plays, Luna Sea Women's Performance Project" [flyer], Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "Valencia Rose Cabaret, Mothertongue Readers' Theatre" [flyer], 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Walnut Street Theatre, Lily Tomlin in "Appearing Nightly," Playbill [program], Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - "Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?," Billy Rose Theatre, Playbill, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Consists of Vol. 1, No. 21.